The Army made Eugene a man. But Daisy gave him basic training!
Biloxi Blues is a comedy, drama, war film directed by Mike Nichols.
A Jewish teenager sets three goals: lose his virginity,
become a writer, and survive World War II.
Eugene Morris Jerome, played by Matthew Broderick.
Sgt. Toomey, played by Christopher Walken.
Joseph Wykowski, played by Matt Mulhern.
Arnold B. Epstein, played by Corey Parker.
Roy Selridge, played by Markus Flanagan.
Don Carney, played by Casey Siemaszko.
Biloxi Blues is a 1988 American military comedy drama film directed by Mike Nichols,
written by Neil Simon, and starring Matthew Broderick and Christopher Walken.
Simon adapted his semi-autobiographical 1984 play of the same title, the second chapter in what is known as
the Eugene trilogy, the first being Brighton Beach Memoirs and the third being Broadway Bound.
The film explores themes of mississippi river, homophobia, world
war ii, based on play or musical, loss of virginity.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.